Throw that mic on, so proud to display Got latex and silicone, ready to slay Smoother, chunky, white, brown, or clear?
Sump or the bathroom, sump or out here?
Colors on the shelf, I can't decide Flexible, waterproof, I'm blown out five Thick as a milkshake, or runny as paint?
Hit the like button, say your job ain't faint Let's see if bunnies start to talk, off on their mic
Gonna get, don't worry, you're gonna find Don't have further doubt, every single line Bolt in your toolbox, gotta use it boy, I can't compete, you dig?
Walked through the store, asked for some caulk Guy at the counter just started to gawp He handed me a tube, I said with a smirk Hope this one fits, I've got a lot of work White or clear, the choice is yours Squeeze that trigger, open those doors Everybody's knocked off of their mind
Donna Depp, don't worry, you're Donna Fonk.
Donna smooth out every single line.
Conking your toolbars, Donny, is it right?
Call Bob, Donna could dine.